

Contact & Details



Email hmyrandeeka@gmail.com

• Address

423/1, Thambugewaththa, Galle
Road, Pamburana, Matara

www.linkedin.com/in/yasas-randeeka

March 23, 1992

LinkedIn

Education

2014 - 2017 BSc (Hons) in Chemical & Process Engineering

University of Moratuwa

2023 - Currently Following

CMJD Professional | Comprehensive Master Java Developer

IJSE | Institute of Software Engineering

2019

Certificate Course in Microsoft Project

Institute of Engineers, Sri Lanka - IESL

Technical Skills

- Programming Languages Java, C#
- Web Development (Front End) HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- Web Development (Back End) -.NET Core framework
- Database Management Oracle SQL, MySQL
- RESTful API Testing- Postman, Jmeter, SoapUI, Katalon Studio
- Test Automation Selenium WebDriver, JUnit, TestNG

H.M. YASAS RANDEEKA

Software Engineer

Profile Summary

Skilled Engineer with 5+ years of professional experience and a zest for solving complex problems. Seeking a challenging career opportunity in a reputed company where I can harness my technical skills and work experience. Become one of the keys for turning the company's vision into realization through strong dedication.

Working Experience

Feb 2023 - Present

Sampath IT Solutions Ltd

(IT Systems Development Department, Sampath Bank PLC)

Software Engineer

Developments & Support Services

- Personalized Score Card in Credit Approval System Development of a new module to check the eligibility of a customer for a loan with a customized questionnaire and evaluation process using .NET Core 5.0 and ReactJS.
- Portfolio SMS Application System Approval Flow modifications using ASP.NET.
- IIS (Internet Information Services) Server .NET Core Application deployments and publishing support services.

QA Automation

- Credit Approval System Testing Automation based on test scenarios using Selenium + Java - UI and Functional tests.
- Document Approval System Testing Automation based on test scenarios using Selenium + Java - UI and Functional tests.

Aug 2020 - Feb 2023

Vogue Tex (Pvt) Ltd I Head Office

Costing Head

- Drive overall optimization of clothing styles based on the engineered cost to achieve profitability.
- 'I Track' Company ERP Development Project

• Feb 2018 - Aug 2020

Vogue Tex (Pvt) Ltd I Weligama Factory

Industrial Engineer

- Plan production styles on a monthly basis and decision making based on actual production.
- Production Layout Optimization Project
- Waste water treatment plant modification project
- QCO (Quick Change Over) process coordination

Languages

- English
- Sinhala

Proffesional Skills

- Creativity
- Leadership
- Adaptability & Flexibility
- Problem-Solving and Critical Thinking
- Collaboration and Teamwork
- Time Management

Reference

Dr. A.D.U. Shantha Amarasinghe

Senior Lecturer,

Department of Chemical & Process Engineering, University of Moratuwa, Sri Lanka.

E-mail: shanthamrt@gmail.com

Phone: +94773064604

Mr. Krishan Jayawardena

Senior Process Engineer, Camso Loadstar Company, Pathegama, Midigama, Weligama, Sri Lanka.

E-mail:

krishan.jayawardena@camso.co

Phone: +94765252943

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

Camso Loadstar (Pvt) Ltd | Midigama Factory

Engineering Trainee

• Trained under the Lean Management & Process Department - Curing time reduction project and cycle time database maintenance.

Projects

Research Project - The Evaluation of Use of Tea Waste Bio -Char (TBC) as Alternative Filler for Natural Rubber (NR)

• Presented the paper at the Annual Session of IESL - 2016

Final Year Research Project - Effect of Nano Lay Reinforcement on Structure and Properties of Natural Rubber Compounds

Final Year Design Project - Hydrogen Peroxide Manufacturing Plant in Sri Lanka

Final Year Design Project - Gasketed Plate Heat Exchanger

Extra-Curricular Activities & Achievements

- Represented University of Moratuwa Badminton B team
- Represented Rahula College at District & All Island Badminton Championships.
- Received school colors for Badminton.
- Represented Rahula College at Chess tournaments.
- Won the third place for Biography Creation at the school Sinhala Literacy Day 2005.

Memberships

- The Institution of Engineers Sri Lanka (IESL) Student Member (2016-2018) & Associate Member (2019-Present)
- Chemical Engineering Student Society (CHESS)- Student Member -University of Moratuwa.
- Member of Classical Music Society University of Moratuwa.